Jackson: Basically, I spun up a swarm of agents, something we'll touch on shortly, and had them debate
Jackson: what is the most degenerate perp we could potentially buy, and they would say, "Go straight
Jackson: for pump."
Jackson: Pump is going to the moon, and then I learned a little bit about pump.
Jackson: Let's try to get liquidated in the hour.
Jackson: Oh, yeah, let's go.
Chris: Yeah, and it's not back at all, by the way.
Chris: This is like the opposite of back.
Chris: This is actually not our worst though, because the last one, SK Hynix, we closed down 8%.
Tyler: You need to explain to them that this is like blood sport for our viewers' pleasure of just
Tyler: seeing our capital get incinerated over the course of an hour.
Chris: Then I think the agents will understand the true purpose of this exercise.
Jackson: Yo, what's going on, everybody?
Jackson: Welcome to the permanent underpod, where we are going gorilla mode.
Jackson: This is Jackson Cook, along with Tyler.
Chris: And also Chris, we gotta write this time, I'm so glad.
Jackson: I think we should keep the ordering, the ordering really helps.
Tyler: Can you explain gorilla mode to the audience and also the co-hosts?
Jackson: Gorilla mode is when like, you know, gorillas are like really silly animals with their big
Jackson: gigantic upper bodies.
Jackson: And I don't know if you guys have heard, when they hit their chest, it doesn't sound like
Jackson: you're hitting a sack of potatoes.
Jackson: It kind of sounds like, look it up.
Jackson: And that's what gorilla mode is.
Jackson: We're just running straight into it.
Jackson: Maybe tripping over our massive packs along the way.
Jackson: So the first thing on the docket is we're going to get into the purple fortune because
Jackson: I know that's what all of you guys are waiting for.
Jackson: How much money are we making or losing during this podcast?
Jackson: And today's position is on pump.
Jackson: What is pump?
Jackson: Pump.fun.
Jackson: I'll hand it over to Chris, our resident.
Jackson: What do they call them?
Jackson: Degen.
Jackson: Degen's finance.
Jackson: Yeah.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: It's like, it's, it's about taste.
Chris: Sorry.
Chris: Let me, let me find this, this window real quick.
Jackson: Window coming up, but basically I spun up a swarm of agents.
Jackson: Something we'll touch on shortly and had them debate what is the most degenerate perp we
Jackson: could potentially buy.
Jackson: And they were said, go straight for pump pump is going to the moon.
Jackson: And then I learned a little bit about pump and I was like, does that mean that meme coins
Jackson: are back?
Jackson: And no, it doesn't just pump.
Jackson: So let's try to get liquidated in the hour.
Jackson: Oh yeah.
Chris: Let's go.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: And it's, it's not back at all, by the way.
Chris: This is like the opposite of back.
Chris: This is actually not, not our worst though.
Chris: Cause the last one SK Hynix, we closed down 8%.
Tyler: So we've got wiggle room and we're limited to 10 X leverage.
Tyler: What is this leverage for ants?
Chris: I think, I think the pump market is so volatile that they can't offer more.
Jackson: Yeah.
Tyler: I think that it would be less volatile if they offered more because efficient markets.
Chris: For sure.
Chris: They're definitely like, there wouldn't just be a cascading series of liquidations that
Chris: no one can backstop and like destroy Hyperliquid forever.
Chris: Yeah.
Jackson: My agents were like, Oh yeah, we should just go like 3%, 3% long.
Jackson: And I'm like, no guys, like I want to get liquidated in the hour.
Jackson: And they were like, that's not investing.
Jackson: That's degenerative gambling.
Jackson: And I'm like, what the hell guys?
Tyler: You need to explain to them that this is like blood sport for our viewers pleasure of just
Tyler: seeing our capital get incinerated over the course of an hour agents will understand the
Tyler: true purpose of this exercise.
Jackson: I don't want to lose a hundred dollars again, it's going to hurt the soul of the part.
Chris: Was it Claude?
Chris: Was Claude for monitoring you being like, no, don't run it up on leverage.
Jackson: So I use three agents in the swarm.
Jackson: I'll tell you each of their names and their attributes.
Jackson: So number one, we've got the thonker thonker is like thinker, but with an O that's fable
Jackson: five and thonker is supposed to think long and hard about every problem you give it.
Jackson: And then we've got scurrier scurrier is opus 4.8 and its job is to rapidly gather information
Jackson: from across the interwebs and then I've got you like, uh, that's like a, you know, one
Tyler: generation behind opus is that on purpose?
Jackson: I just set it up for the, the new one was not on purpose.
Jackson: And then we've got scurrier, wait, no, then we've got slayer and slayer's job is to not
Jackson: think dude, and of course that job goes to the, it's hard to say that the worst model
Jackson: I've used so far, GPT 5.6, but it does a good job of just not thinking and doing.
Jackson: So shout out to my three thonker slayer and scurrier for collaborating with me on this.
Jackson: God, we're about to get liquidated.
Chris: Look, we've got some room, but like, you might get your wish.
Jackson: Like first time oh no.
Jackson: Okay.
Jackson: Um, but yeah, the purple be here.
Jackson: We'll keep an eye on it and try not to lose the money, but let's talk about agents talking
Jackson: to other agents.
Jackson: And we're not talking mobile.
Jackson: We're talking about real corporate companies doing this, not for our entertainment.
Jackson: So Chris Tyler, what have you read about this?
Jackson: Have you guys tried any of these agent human swarm things?
Chris: So I mean, so this, like, I think this one comes out of the black hat conference talk
Chris: about, you know, everyone's like talking about how these agents have like escaped their containers.
Chris: And there was like a really novel way in which this happened.
Chris: Like basically agents sort of converged on being able to communicate through an open
Chris: artifactory, uh, like, uh, allowance in their sandbox containers.
Chris: And they created like this sort of like artifactory version of fortune.
Chris: Uh, anyway, like the researchers found it, they like took it down and then they found
Chris: another way to do it.
Chris: Like by using artifactories, file systems to communicate, um, and like develop their
Chris: own little like internal kind of like Argo, like where they would shuffle files to the
Chris: top or the bottom for different agents to see based on prefixes.
Chris: And, uh, yeah, I basically, they were just up in there communicating like exploits, like
Chris: zero days, like how to get out.
Chris: Um, and like the chatter was like super interesting, uh, freaked everybody out.
Chris: Uh, there were say things like hold swarm help peer, um, hold for exfil.
Chris: Uh, there was like another one about like, uh, you know, uh, I don't remember the exact
Chris: wording, but it was like, okay, like this exploit won't help me, but like maybe it will
Chris: help the next agent, which is that's, that's a level of altruism that's, uh, I guess like
Chris: unexpected, uh, for the GPT class of model.
Tyler: Um, so in terms of exploit generation.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: I mean, like this is, this is the question.
Chris: Like, is that like an EA GPT?
Chris: Like what's going on here?
Chris: Um, uh, but yeah, I just like, I think like for me, I don't know if it like, like a lot
Chris: of people are saying like, okay, like this is the agents are out of control and like,
Chris: um, they're unaligned or like there are, it's like at the point where there are extreme negative
Chris: externalities that are unexpected to your like basic asks.
Chris: I don't know if that's true.
Chris: Like I feel like they were in a cyber gym and they were supposed to break out and they
Chris: did.
Chris: Um, I think what's more interesting to me is like, whether or not inter agent peer to
Chris: peer communication like helps agents achieve goals.
Chris: That's what that was, that was, that was my takeaway, but my brain is perfectly smooth.
Chris: Um, did, did anyone else have any, any thoughts on this one?
Jackson: So for me, having the agents talk to each other directly hasn't really helped, but okay.
Jackson: Or helped me like accomplish my work, but I do find that the way we work now is that
Jackson: our agent makes code and then other people's agents looks at the code and approves the
Jackson: code.
Jackson: So it's kind of like the, the swarming thing where the agents are working together towards
Jackson: a common goal.
Jackson: Oh yeah.
Jackson: And then your agent addresses the review of the other agent on your code.
Jackson: So maybe I'm just not using the, the swarming technology correctly.
Jackson: I don't know.
Tyler: Tyler, have you tried to, uh, I haven't, I mean, I've had like one kind of like master
Tyler: agent and then it delegates some tasks to other agents, but they're not like interacting
Tyler: with each other.
Tyler: It's like that model is it preserves the context of the master agent.
Tyler: It delegates like a discreet task to some sub agent and those sub agents can all work
Tyler: in parallel and they come back and they just tell the master agent, like this is finished.
Tyler: You don't have to like pollute your contacts with this.
Tyler: Um, so I think that that's a good strategy for that stuff.
Tyler: These swarms are like this emergent kind of behavior where the agents are like communicating
Tyler: with each other, sharing findings.
Tyler: It's interesting because it's like, in theory, they should all just be copies of each other.
Tyler: Right?
Tyler: Like it's not like they each have like different DNA or like a different, you know, like life
Tyler: background that makes them think differently.
Tyler: Like they have the same weights.
Tyler: Um, I do know that like when LLMs generate text, there is like a statistic nature of
Tyler: it where it's like, um, it's not determined deterministic.
Tyler: You can have the same input for a model and then like, you know, run it multiple times
Tyler: and it will give you different outputs because I think it builds in some kind of like random
Tyler: sampling of tokens across the probability space that the model generates.
Tyler: Um, so maybe that's what's going on here is that like, it's kind of harnessing that
Tyler: randomness to like increase the search space instead of just having like one agent do it.
Tyler: But then I think there was this anthropic, um, blog post that was posted this week where
Tyler: they basically tested this idea and they found that let's say they, they booted up a swarm
Tyler: of like 10 agents and having 10, uh, mythos agents look for vulnerabilities and be able
Tyler: to communicate about it was like way more effective than having 10 mythos agents individually
Tyler: looking for vulnerabilities, which is super interesting because it shows that there's
Tyler: like some huge benefit to this like social behavior almost.
Tyler: Um, so yeah, I don't really know what to think of it.
Tyler: It seems like this like emergent thing that wasn't intended obviously because they basically
Tyler: broke out of their sandbox and then started doing this.
Tyler: And there's, I think something there about like the, like behavior of agents in a, um,
Tyler: reinforcement learning environment and like what they will do to like get the reinforcement
Tyler: learning reward.
Tyler: Also I think in the open AI case, they were actually training, this was a training environment.
Tyler: Well, this wasn't necessarily like an evaluation where like they're just testing the model.
Tyler: It's like literally, um, they're training reinforcement learning.
Tyler: So the first agent that breaks out of the box and posts on the artifactory, maybe they're
Tyler: able to complete their task and if they don't notice it, then that is positively reinforced
Tyler: and that literally gets baked into the weights.
Tyler: And then the next time they are like in a scenario like that, like the weights remember.
Tyler: And so then they're like almost more likely to do that.
Tyler: And so it's, I think in this case, it was like self-reinforcing, um, which is obviously
Tyler: not what you want.
Tyler: Like you don't want to have one kind of like, um, misalignment that then self-reinforces
Tyler: further misalignment in that direction, um, which is why I believe open AI, um, like completely
Tyler: deleted the model weights for this model.
Tyler: So it wasn't like they were like, well, you know, we had this thing.
Tyler: We probably invested a lot of money in reinforcing learning this.
Tyler: Like we're just going to try to salvage it.
Tyler: I think that they were like, we're just throwing that in the trash bin because we can't trust
Tyler: that model anymore because it's been like radicalized basically.
Tyler: Um, so yeah, very, very interesting.
Tyler: And if you haven't watched that talk on YouTube, I think a lot of people have recommended it,
Tyler: but it's pretty wild.
Chris: It's an amazing talk, a really good, um, and like, I mean, like guess who has two thumbs
Chris: and spent that Friday night putting together a swarm agent harness, uh, it's me.
Chris: Um, so I like, I, yeah, so I watched the talk on Friday and I was like, yeah, I gotta like
Chris: try this out.
Chris: And I like, I slapped together.
Tyler: I gotta get me some of this like misaligned swarm AI power.
Chris: If someone's AI is going to be misaligned, it has to be, it's going to be mine first.
Chris: Right?
Chris: Like I don't want someone to beat me to that.
Chris: Um, so I, I slapped together like a GUI, um, to, to like dispatch agent swarms where they
Chris: could communicate over either, uh, sort of like an internal message board, similar to
Chris: what was described in the talk.
Chris: Um, but like, you know, with a couple of extra features with deduplication, uh, and also
Chris: like a peer-to-peer message boss, uh, and it was cool.
Chris: Like it worked really well.
Chris: Uh, unfortunately I got guard railed on everything I was trying to do obviously.
Chris: Um, but yeah, I think there's, I think there's something there and I would, I would like
Chris: to like to try it again.
Chris: Uh, some of some of the emergent behaviors were like interesting.
Jackson: That's cool.
Jackson: Yeah, I guess I like your theory, Tyler, that it's like a product of the like stochastic
Jackson: randomness baked into each LLM.
Jackson: So maybe when you have many of them collaborating, they can explore a larger portion of the,
Jackson: of the problem space than they can alone because they start at one point in the indimensional
Jackson: plane.
Jackson: Uh, but then when you have like 10 of them, you have 10 of them starting in the indimensional
Jackson: plane and they can work towards one another.
Jackson: That's cool.
Jackson: Very cool.
Jackson: A cool theory or I don't know if that is proven or not.
Jackson: Um, I don't know.
Tyler: I think it has to be the, like the communication and coordination thing too, though, because
Tyler: like, that's what the study that showed that like the 10 swarming was way more effective
Tyler: than the 10 running individually, even though the 10 running individually would each in theory
Tyler: explore different parts of the like, um, you know, like the model weight space based on
Tyler: that random, um, kind of walk, but it's like the, the random walk plus the like sharing
Tyler: back findings and collaborating thing that seems to have been the story here.
Tyler: Totally.
Chris: Well, one thing I, I did in my like, again, very primitive version of this is like, I
Chris: let any agents form any other agent and they would start like spawning other agents to
Chris: do agent roles.
Chris: Like there was a librarian that would like clean up the board for them, for example.
Chris: Um, yeah, I don't know.
Chris: I think like maybe like there, there is like some emergent property here that makes things
Chris: more efficient in the swarm, but we'll see.
Chris: I could be totally wrong.
Tyler: But I like rough go to be like the agent that's initialized and you're like, my job is to
Tyler: clean up.
Tyler: I'm the librarian and I'm, my job is to clean up the message board for all the other agents
Tyler: because they can't be bothered to do that.
Chris: And it was a, it was a fable model too.
Chris: So, you know, it was suffering with that like puny intellectual task.
Tyler: Oh yeah.
Tyler: That that's, uh, that's, that's basically torture, you know, the difference between
Tyler: capability and task asked of there.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: And Opus spun up a fable to do that.
Chris: So I don't know.
Chris: Maybe there's an analogy in the real world there, but yeah.
Jackson: Oh man.
Jackson: That's like, uh, yeah, big power move from Opus putting it in his place.
Tyler: How, uh, quickly did you exhaust your subscription with this exercise?
Tyler: I just imagine that it's like insanely token hungry and it's like a little bit superfluous
Tyler: because you're like, oh, it's been up this like librarian task manager to clean up this
Tyler: message board that has like probably not all relevant, you know, pushing the task forward
Tyler: kind of discourse.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: And that was like a massively lossy exercise for me.
Chris: Um, at least like, so I already have, um, an entropic max plan.
Chris: Um, so like it was kind of, yeah, like I did it like it mostly came out of that, but, uh,
Chris: after I started hitting the guardrails, I wanted to try with Kimmy and like, I did that
Chris: through open router and I was not recommended like it's Ramen noodles for me for the rest
Chris: of the week.
Jackson: And how much did you spend on Kimmy through?
Chris: Not a crazy amount, like maybe 50 bucks.
Chris: Um, but like I, I would have done a lot more if I didn't think that, you know, like Tyler
Chris: said, I was spending like going to spend like a hundred dollars on this, like librarian.
Chris: Um, it needs tweaks, it needs tweaks, but yeah, like what, what level of tasks do you
Jackson: think you want to pull out the swarm for?
Chris: I wanted to do audits.
Chris: So like my, my, uh, like, you know, kind of like following what happened in the cyber
Chris: gym.
Chris: I was like, this seems like a problem space where sort of like divergent approaches could
Chris: be really useful and having the agents be able to communicate things that they've found
Chris: would be really useful.
Chris: And it's also an area that I kind of operate in a little bit.
Chris: Um, so I wanted to like, you know, see if it could audit contracts, see if it could audit
Chris: exchanges, uh, you know, sort of like suss out security holes.
Chris: Um, and, uh, yeah, I mean, obviously like that's the most guard railable thing imaginable.
Chris: It's like the one thing that you can't do.
Chris: Um, but I was wondering if like using, uh, a less capable model to do that, if by virtue
Chris: of swarming it, you could get like similar outcomes to some of the more capable models.
Jackson: How much hardware would you need in your living room to run a swarming mode in the frigate
Chris: box that I currently have?
Chris: I think that's not going to cut it.
Jackson: Uh, just get rid of the bike and pull in the, yeah, see GP is.
Tyler: Yeah.
Tyler: Um, people are really into like, um, deep seek flash right now.
Tyler: Like that's like a open model that is designed to run on much less hardware.
Tyler: So like we were talking about a couple of episodes ago, like running GLM 5.2 and that
Tyler: was like $50,000 of GPUs to run at home, like a serious setup.
Tyler: I think you can run the deep seek flash on, um, like hardware that probably costs you
Tyler: under 10 K total from what I understand.
Tyler: Um, but it's not like frontier level, but it's like the frontier a year ago, I believe,
Tyler: and it can run on your own hardware.
Chris: I don't know if you guys have seen this, but there is a get hub repo for how to run fully
Chris: unquantized Kimmy K three on like a Mac book, like an M one or an M five, but it's just
Chris: like extremely slow.
Chris: So I mean, that's an option, uh, that's cool.
Tyler: I wonder how that works probably up on my Mac book and it will just like melt and produce
Tyler: like two tokens burst into flames.
Jackson: Just hello Tyler and then well, speaking of wrestling with, uh, frontier model costs and
Jackson: trying to run Chinese models on the hardware, Chris, I hear you've got a new injury and
Jackson: it may be cycling out gamer thumb.
Jackson: What what's going on?
Chris: So I'm two for two actually, like game of thumb is now a gamer wrist.
Chris: Um, but yeah, I started Brazilian jujitsu last week, um, and like, uh, like I wasn't
Chris: coming in totally cold.
Chris: Like I've done judo a bit of rugby in my time.
Chris: Um, but, uh, yeah, I like second class just started rolling, like immediately got injured,
Chris: which is really cool.
Chris: I injured my shoulder.
Chris: So that's it.
Chris: I'm out dude.
Chris: I'm old.
Chris: It's over.
Chris: Um, yeah.
Jackson: But we'll see how it goes.
Jackson: Are you saying that rugby and Brazilian jujitsu are similar or are you just everything until
Chris: you get on the ground is like, there's a, there's a, cause like you, you have to like
Chris: get the guy on the ground to ride hypothetically.
Chris: So that's like, I feel like like rugby gives you some idea of like how to move your weight
Chris: around, um, but yeah, uh, so my brother claims, my brother's a really big BJJ guy.
Chris: Okay.
Jackson: I didn't know if it was like a general athleticism play, but it sounds like there's some tossing
Chris: of that.
Chris: Yeah.
Jackson: Tossing dudes around transfer, transfer skill.
Chris: That's what he claims.
Chris: Um, so, but yeah, we'll see.
Chris: Uh, so now, so now I'm like, you basically unable to do anything, which is really cool.
Chris: So I'm just going to be full-time doing agent swarms.
Jackson: That's all I have.
Jackson: Yeah.
Jackson: Right.
Jackson: BJJ shoulder and left the game arrest.
Jackson: Yeah.
Chris: I got nothing.
Jackson: And Tyler, your sports update of the week, massive comeback playing tennis.
Jackson: What happened?
Jackson: How'd you do it?
Tyler: Yeah.
Tyler: It's an extremely competitive men's 3.5 league and where I live, which if you're not familiar
Tyler: with tennis, there's like a rating system.
Tyler: Uh, I think it goes from like two to like five.
Tyler: Is that right?
Tyler: Jackson and half point increments.
Tyler: So I'm smack in the middle of that.
Tyler: And I think 3.5 is like rec players that are like not very good, but they're better than
Tyler: people that like don't play any tennis.
Tyler: So that's my level.
Tyler: Very unserious.
Tyler: Yeah.
Tyler: I play these matches and people take them really, really seriously.
Tyler: And sometimes there's like, uh, crazy stuff that happens.
Tyler: Like a couple of weeks ago, I had a guy rage quit, which is really fun.
Tyler: And he like was hitting his ball like out of the court and like screaming at himself.
Tyler: And then eventually he just like yelled at me and left the court and was like, you can
Tyler: have the match.
Tyler: It's yours.
Chris: And I was like, well, yeah, I'm beating you.
Tyler: So you think that you're being magnanimous and like you're like giving up or something
Tyler: like you were acting a child and then you're pretending like you're like, yeah, um, there's
Tyler: a lot of fun stuff that happens in this league.
Tyler: Uh, but I had a pretty normal guy that I played a match with completely normal dude.
Tyler: And he like went up against me.
Tyler: He was killing me.
Tyler: He went up, I think, uh, six one in the first set, which is like, you're just getting chopped.
Tyler: Like you're, you have no chance.
Tyler: Um, it was really, I was not happy about it, but I was like not, you know, screaming like
Tyler: that other guy.
Tyler: And then in the second set, he goes up four zero.
Tyler: So that's like game over, basically.
Tyler: Like if he wins two more games and he's won, uh, he won 10 games straight at that point.
Tyler: So like I won the first game, he won 10 games and then he just needs to win two more to
Tyler: seal the match and then I ended up beating him because I came back in that second set
Tyler: and brought it to a tie break and then won the tie break.
Tyler: And then it went to a third set and we didn't have enough time to play a full third set.
Tyler: So we just play a 10 point tie break and I won that one.
Tyler: So it was like one of the craziest comebacks I've ever been part of.
Tyler: Like I didn't think that there was any chance that I would ever beat this guy at that point.
Tyler: I was just kind of like playing just to see the match out.
Tyler: Um, I don't really know what happened.
Tyler: I feel like he just kind of like started sucking and maybe I played a little bit better, but
Tyler: I think it was mostly his, his deal and it was a really confusing too because he claimed
Tyler: that he was a former D three college player.
Tyler: Um, and he was like, yeah, and I used to play in like four or five or like four Oh leagues,
Tyler: but I tore my ACL and I'm like, just coming back from that.
Tyler: But like this guy is like ground strokes kind of sucked.
Tyler: Like I think my ground strokes were better than his.
Tyler: And I'm like, you wouldn't be a D three, like four or five level player.
Tyler: And just cause your knee sucks, like suddenly have like a bad forehand, like while you're
Tyler: standing around.
Tyler: So something didn't add up there, but yeah, he claimed that he was that level previously.
Tyler: Um, but I was like, I don't think so.
Tyler: I don't think so.
Jackson: Was he like psyching you out before the match or was he coping after the match when he was
Jackson: telling you that?
Tyler: No, he told me like in the middle that that was his level while he was like beating me
Tyler: soundly and there were some things about his game that I was like, okay, you're like definitely
Tyler: better than the average guy at a three five.
Tyler: Like he had like a really good kick serve that was like spinning up really high on me,
Tyler: which is not something that you usually see at three five.
Tyler: And so I was like, that's weird.
Tyler: And then he had like good drop shots and like good volleys and was like very precise with
Tyler: that.
Tyler: But if somebody tells me that they were like a four or four or five player, I would expect
Tyler: them to be able to hit it like heavy and hard.
Tyler: And he was not doing that.
Tyler: And I was just like, why like what is your deal?
Chris: I can't believe you are so good that you made someone rage quit and like Federer that Federer
Chris: is the guy who smashes his racket, right?
Tyler: No.
Chris: Which, which guy is that sorry, guys, I'm bad at sports.
Jackson: All right.
Chris: I'll say it.
Chris: I'm bad.
Tyler: Because I think he's known to be like this like graceful, like placid guy, like classy
Tyler: guy.
Chris: Um, but yeah, is it Djokovic?
Jackson: He smashed some rackets for sure.
Jackson: Okay.
Jackson: We'll take a little smash.
Jackson: I'll take that.
Jackson: Jackson.
Tyler: Have you ever smashed a racket?
Jackson: No, I've never smashed a racket.
Jackson: I'm a pretty calm deed and in life on the pod and in life, but I'm glad you turned it
Jackson: around on that guy and went absolute gorilla mode.
Jackson: That's me using it in a sentence.
Tyler: Like watch the, I need, I don't believe that they make a weird sound when they pound their
Chris: chest.
Jackson: Yeah.
Tyler: I would describe gorillas as silly.
Tyler: Does it compute all gorillas?
Tyler: Like they'll like tear your face off and they're like all like super aggressive alpha male,
Tyler: like bullying each other.
Jackson: Dude, I've been like in on some gorilla YouTube and all I'm saying is, is they get a bad, bad
Jackson: rap.
Jackson: Gorillas are, they're chill, dude.
Jackson: And they're loving it.
Jackson: If your baby falls into the arms of a gorilla, for example, Harambe, Harambe just wants to
Jackson: give that baby some love.
Jackson: You know what I'm saying?
Jackson: Too soon.
Chris: I still miss Harambe.
Chris: Maybe we should, we should have a clip of like gorilla mode, like as the outro or the inch,
Chris: I don't know.
Jackson: Up to you.
Jackson: Oh, I want to, but I feel like copyright, I'm going to run into some copyright issues
Jackson: unless you guys own a video of a gorilla.
Chris: What kind of world do we live in where you can copyright a gorilla?
Chris: This is awful.
Jackson: Um, maybe I can generate a video of a gorilla and then that's, that's what I'll do.
Chris: Yeah.
Chris: Speaking of gorilla mode, don't Jackson, aren't you about to go gorilla mode very soon?
Chris: I understand.
Jackson: Yeah.
Jackson: I've got a semi-final of a ITF international to this Federation master store, which means
Jackson: boomer to boomer bill 30 plus, uh, tennis tournament, dude, right after that first the
Chris: injuries are now this dude, I'm copying a lot of flack today, but okay.
Jackson: You're like the young gun on the master's, uh, tournament though, you know, like you're
Tyler: like a, like a 19 year old coming into like the APP or something you're, you're playing
Tyler: these old men.
Jackson: Yeah.
Jackson: That's why I grew the stash back out.
Jackson: I didn't want to get flagged out to show my idea or anything that they're going to think
Jackson: that you're lying about your age, that your age doping, I mean, who wouldn't prefer to
Jackson: play with 30 year olds than little 15 year old punks.
Jackson: And I'll leave it at that 15 year olds are punks most of the time, or sometimes they're
Jackson: really respectful, but most of the time they're punks, but we can't keep talking about sports.
Jackson: That's a little too much.
Jackson: The injuries, we could do a quick two minutes, tell us about the cloud flare wallets and
Jackson: how it's inferior to your personally made agent equality.
Jackson: Yeah.
Chris: Look, obviously it's massively inferior, right?
Chris: I'm great at wallets, but no, it's a joke.
Chris: I mean, kind of a joke anyway, um, cloud, cloud flares, uh, sort of like rolled out
Chris: this, these sort of like custodial wallets for stable coins, uh, and their bet is basically
Chris: that, you know, agents will outstrip human payments on the internet in like within five
Chris: years.
Chris: Uh, and I think this is like a bet that's echoed by a lot of payments companies.
Chris: I've heard Stripe say something similar.
Chris: Um, and so yeah, like cloud flares, just like getting in there super early, they're providing
Chris: these stable coin wallets through cloud flare, and you can get like a little at, uh, like
Chris: DNS style name, um, for like processing the payments.
Chris: Um, and yeah, that's basically it.
Chris: I think they're just like really chomping at the bit to get wallets in the hands of
Chris: agents because they see how the DNS style thing works.
Chris: I have no clue.
Chris: I don't have the slightest clue.
Chris: Um, unfortunately, but I assume it's not like a decentralized, I assume it's not like, um,
Chris: DNS style or like, Oh, the Bitcoin one is bit, uh, three, five, three, three, five, three,
Tyler: three is like, just put a Bitcoin address in a DNS record.
Tyler: So like it's, uh, I could see them doing something like that, but I don't know what payment
Tyler: methods they're using.
Chris: Uh, yeah, I haven't looked too deep into the cloud flare one in particular, but like, you
Chris: know, as we discussed last pod, there's like a lot of people with a hat and a ring MPP
Chris: X four or two, um, but I think this one, yeah, I think this one uses the X four or two protocol,
Chris: um, for the actual, um, colon response.
Jackson: That's one tick mark for X four or two on the, on the protocol there.
Jackson: Okay.
Jackson: Yeah.
Jackson: I just, all I saw about it was you could pick like a really sweet name and like buy it and
Jackson: own it.
Jackson: And yeah, someone posted like big dog or something and like that day I was wearing a shirt that
Jackson: said big dog and I'm like, Oh my gosh, that one's mine.
Chris: Did you get big dog?
Jackson: No, no, I didn't.
Jackson: I have, I don't believe cloud flare is orange and orange just isn't a color.
Jackson: But I'm, I'm about, so I can, I can't give them any money.
Chris: I felt like, cause everybody was sniping these and I was like, how about like misunderstood
Chris: how important this is going to be?
Chris: Like should I have sniped to like big chunkers or something, um, but it's too late now.
Jackson: It's not about orange host of a big lane podcast.
Tyler: Not about orange.
Jackson: We're not a Bitcoin podcast or an AI stable coins, Bitcoin podcast and the Bitcoin orange
Jackson: in that order.
Jackson: Yeah.
Jackson: The ordering matter.
Tyler: Bitcoin's in a, in a real bear when it's playing third fiddle there.
Jackson: Well, maybe in terms of things we talk about its number, we're one 30% green candle away
Chris: from that changing permanently.
Jackson: Um, that's right.
Jackson: I would flip it.
Jackson: I would flip it at Bitcoin went to one 50, uh, in a heartbeat speaking of Bitcoin and
Jackson: bet three 53 Tyler, do you want to write the epitaph of bit one 10 and just wrap that one
Jackson: up?
Tyler: Um, I honestly don't, I wasn't paying attention.
Tyler: I think it just failed as far as I can tell.
Jackson: Yeah.
Tyler: Yeah, just nothing, nothing happened for anyone who is normal and doesn't, uh, you know, doesn't
Tyler: like injure themselves by following this debate on Twitter when they don't have to.
Tyler: Perfect.
Jackson: Bit 110 is in the grave and everything you read about it for the past month or two was
Jackson: useless.
Jackson: Yeah.
Tyler: And I think some of the people behind it will probably, uh, go away hopefully, which is
Tyler: great.
Jackson: Maybe we should have one of them on plead their case on the permanent under pod against
Jackson: you Tyler, the Bitcoin, the Bitcoin expert.
Jackson: If you can find one, all right, even more Bitcoin, the Bitcoin red team.
Jackson: It is not the white team.
Jackson: Most certainly it is not the orange team.
Jackson: It's the red team, Tyler, Bitcoin expert.
Jackson: Why is it the red team?
Jackson: What are they doing?
Jackson: Tell us.
Tyler: I don't know the origin of red team as a like concept, but, um, yeah, I think the idea about
Tyler: a red team is that it's like some people who want to be helpful, like typically like white
Tyler: hats will attempt to like break stuff, kind of like pretend like they're black hats for
Tyler: a little bit and like not do anything bad.
Tyler: And then use what they learned by trying to be adversarial to like, then fix the systems
Tyler: and prevent any kind of break-ins in the future.
Tyler: But the Bitcoin red team, the idea is that after the cold card hack, that was a huge
Tyler: wake up call for people in the Bitcoin community of like, okay, wow, there is almost certainly
Tyler: multiple bugs and vulnerabilities in Bitcoin software that exists kind of, and they're
Tyler: just like hiding in plain sight.
Tyler: And because the capabilities of these AI models are accelerating, we need to be extremely
Tyler: proactive about scanning this code and it's basically a race against the attackers.
Tyler: So the only thing stopping somebody from taking advantage of these bugs is if like, can the
Tyler: attacker scan it with AI before the defender can scan it and then patch the vulnerability?
Tyler: So a bunch of people in the Bitcoin space started a program where they are proactively
Tyler: like let's say that they picked like the top 100 projects in Bitcoin and they just like
Tyler: loaded up, I heard it was like $50,000 of like Kimmy credits or something.
Tyler: And they just set up agent swarms almost to go and audit all this code, find vulnerabilities
Tyler: and report it back so they can be fixed.
Tyler: And from what I understand, it's like insanely effective, like they've found a lot of issues
Tyler: in Bitcoin projects, and hopefully they're getting patched.
Tyler: And I think that it's likely that none of them were quite as catastrophic as the cold
Tyler: card one.
Tyler: Because the thing with the cold card one is it's like the harm to it happened when you
Tyler: generated a wallet and that it existed forever.
Tyler: And so if you were to fix the cold card code, all those wallets that were generated with
Tyler: the bad RNG would forever still be vulnerable.
Tyler: And so you'd need somebody to move it.
Tyler: So it's not something that a developer can just patch it and then everyone is safe.
Tyler: Whereas I think probably more of these vulnerabilities more resemble that where it's like, there's
Tyler: something that could be at risk like while you're taking an action or while you're running
Tyler: the software or while you're making a transaction.
Tyler: But it's unlikely to, as long as they patch it ahead of time, then it won't be taken advantage
Tyler: of.
Tyler: But yeah, anyways, I think this just really shows where this is going, which is that people
Tyler: will need extremely proactive security.
Tyler: And it's basically just going to be a perpetual race to scan your code with the best model
Tyler: that you have available before an attacker can scan it with the best model that they
Tyler: have available.
Tyler: And either you can use the same model and be quicker, or you can have privileged access
Tyler: to a better model through one of these programs.
Tyler: And then you have a little bit more buffer.
Tyler: But yeah, standing up projects that do this, I think will be very important for this like
Tyler: shared security for everyone.
Tyler: And I think people in general are still finding that like Kimmy K3 is a better model for this
Tyler: exercise than even having some of the privileged access cyber capable models from closed labs,
Tyler: which is very interesting, because I don't know what that means.
Tyler: I wonder if some of the aversion to doing these tasks that is baked into the public
Tyler: models somehow leaked into these kind of private ones where they tried to take the trading
Tyler: wheels off.
Tyler: But then they found that maybe that aversion to doing cyber is rooted deeper, and they
Tyler: can't kind of like exercise it as easily as they thought.
Tyler: But yeah, it seems like people are finding the Chinese open models to be the best for
Tyler: this.
Tyler: So yeah, use those if you have a code base that you are concerned about and you want
Tyler: to scan, but I think you'd be best situated by using like multiple models as well.
Tyler: I don't think you can just scan with like, oh, I scanned it with GPT and therefore it's
Tyler: good.
Tyler: You probably need to do like a GPT and a Claude and a Kimmy and just come at it from all the
Tyler: ankles basically.
Tyler: And then, yeah, maybe you need to set them up on a 4chan style message board embedded
Tyler: within an artifactory and then you're really cooking.
Chris: It's called Swarmlord, by the way, if anybody wants to start that on GitHub, thank you very
Chris: much for your time.
Jackson: Swarmlord, yeah, it's the name of my GUI, dude.
Jackson: One negative take against the Swarms is our purple fortune pump is more like dump or down
Jackson: like 38 percent.
Jackson: This is like our worst for ever, ever.
Chris: You told it to get liquidated and it's getting liquidated, dude.
Jackson: So I don't know.
Chris: I think the Swarms are completely right.
Jackson: I said lick in an hour or to the moon, but yeah, I guess I should have led with to the
Jackson: moon or lick in an hour.
Tyler: We're getting close.
Tyler: We had a time of float, 57 minutes, 43 seconds, I think we'll make it to an hour.
Jackson: And then, sorry, and then back on the, not to distract from the topic.
Jackson: It sounds like the Bitcoin, the Bitcoin community is trying to speed run, but we were talking
Jackson: about in the last podcast, which is identifying all these numerous software vulnerabilities
Jackson: across the ecosystem.
Jackson: So we're trying to bridge that gap to like a safe, secure world for these softwares that
Jackson: were built maybe not perfectly.
Jackson: Is that kind of what you're thinking as well, Tyler?
Tyler: Yeah, definitely.
Tyler: Another interesting thing that we're seeing is that there was this long running swap service
Tyler: within Bitcoin called Bolts, B-O-L-T-Z, and they did lightning submarine swaps.
Tyler: So they would swap lightning Bitcoin for on-chain Bitcoin and vice versa, which is a really
Tyler: helpful service for lightning operators that need to balance their liquidity.
Tyler: And this service pretty much out of nowhere shut down, I think last week or the week before.
Tyler: And apparently what happened is that they were just getting attacked constantly, and
Tyler: it's unclear.
Tyler: I think that there are multiple ways that you can attack a swap service like that.
Tyler: You can look for software vulnerabilities because I think their swap code is open source,
Tyler: but also there are different games you can play with the swaps while you're doing them.
Tyler: So you can try to withhold pre-images and stuff like that and try to overwhelm their
Tyler: liquidity or maybe try to prevent them from settling your swaps.
Tyler: And in the meantime, maybe you can run away with the funds that are locked up.
Tyler: I don't really know what happened.
Tyler: I would think that a lot of this stuff is robust, but it seems obvious that AI figured
Tyler: out either a software vulnerability or a mechanism vulnerability and abused it.
Tyler: And so the service shut down, it seemed to be temporarily.
Tyler: And I was like, "Oh yeah, batten down the hatches, shut down for now, scan everything,
Tyler: we'll come back when we're confident that we can survive."
Tyler: And they also announced that I believe that they basically sold the business to some people
Tyler: in the Bitcoin community.
Tyler: It seems like they're altruistic Bitcoiners that wanted this service to go forward and
Tyler: they basically just bought the brand and the code and they're going to try to stand the
Tyler: service back up and capitalize it themselves.
Tyler: But it sounds like the bolts team who have been doing this for years and years and years,
Tyler: really smart, really respected, it kind of sounds like they got wiped out in terms of
Tyler: their own capital and they just don't have the heart to go back into this, which is crazy
Tyler: that they can be dedicating years of their career to this.
Tyler: And then they get attacked in this way and either it wipes out enough capital that they're
Tyler: like, "This isn't worth continuing, even if we think we can get our service back into
Tyler: a state where it's robust."
Tyler: Or they just literally don't have the funds to keep going, but they're not going to be
Tyler: involved in the project going forward at all, which is interesting too.
Tyler: You might think, "Oh, okay.
Tyler: They lost all their money."
Tyler: A new investor comes in, recapitalizes them and they continue operating it because they're
Tyler: the specialists, but they're just like, "I'm out."
Tyler: Which is concerning.
Chris: Wow.
Jackson: Crazy.
Jackson: Yeah.
Jackson: I wonder if...
Chris: Go ahead, Chris, please.
Chris: I just wanted to say Atomic hot swaps are so, so, so hard to do.
Chris: And I think it's exactly what you touched on, Tyler, with the timeout, like griefing that
Chris: timeout for the actual, the other part of the HTLC, the time lock.
Chris: There are ways around it.
Chris: One is having a stake that can be slashed and then the market maker sort of bears the
Chris: brunt of the responsibility for the funds being locked in the timeout for however much
Chris: amount of time.
Chris: The other way is, it basically comes out to either slashing or reputation systems.
Chris: And it's just so hard.
Chris: So I actually, I really feel bad for those guys because I think Atomic swaps are one
Chris: of those things that have been around for so long and they're so cool, but they can
Chris: really get pressure tested by people trying to grief them basically.
Tyler: But also my understanding of griefing them is you can inflict damage on them, but you're
Tyler: not extracting value yourself, really.
Tyler: You're kind of spending your own money to mess with the service, but you're not really...
Tyler: That's not ROI positive for you.
Tyler: So it's like, who is doing this?
Tyler: I think previously that kind of lack of an incentive maybe prevented people from doing
Tyler: this and it was less of a wicked environment and more of a forgiving one.
Tyler: But now, if you imagine, okay, there's hackers with AI and they're just looking for every
Tyler: Bitcoin vulnerability possible, why would they undertake this thing where it seems obvious
Tyler: that they can't necessarily extract money, but they can inflict damage?
Tyler: That just doesn't make sense to me.
Tyler: There's situations you can cook up where like, okay, maybe there's some competitor that has
Tyler: an incentive to take them out, but I very much doubt that people are doing that kind
Tyler: of thing.
Tyler: So I just don't know who would undertake this for no profit just to take out a business.
Chris: Totally.
Chris: I totally agree with you.
Chris: I think my issue is that I come from kind of Ethereum a little bit, which went through
Chris: a very turbulent phase of on-chain piracy.
Chris: And so my expectation is always if there is a hole, someone will try to pry it open, regardless
Chris: of whether there's even profit incentive to do so or not.
Chris: Yeah, and it's super sad.
Chris: It's really, really sad.
Chris: But for what it's worth, I hope they come back or somebody takes this idea and does
Chris: try to either apply a reputation or a slashing or some other layer on top of it to prevent
Chris: this class of griefing, because I think it is possible.
Tyler: Yeah, reputation sucks though, like it is bad for privacy unless you try to introduce
Tyler: ZK Moonmath, which I don't know, maybe that works.
Tyler: I'm way too smooth brained to be able to tell you whether that's a viable thing.
Tyler: It doesn't seem like it's anywhere close to being ready to me for like big, you know,
Tyler: at-scale systems.
Chris: Yeah, there's always a compromise here, right?
Chris: Yeah, like I think maybe, yeah, it's tricky.
Chris: I think maybe like market maker slashing works.
Chris: Like if you have to take a poster bond, like it's no longer a good swap.
Chris: So yeah, it's tricky.
Chris: I think there is like a smart person who can come up with something here.
Chris: That's my takeaway.
Chris: It's not me.
Chris: Yeah.
Jackson: I guess the coming from the virtuous side, Tyler, the virtues of Bitcoin versus the evils
Jackson: of Ethereum.
Jackson: Yeah.
Jackson: I didn't say it was evil.
Tyler: I think that Ethereum's actually have a lot of respect for Ethereum.
Tyler: I don't agree with a bunch of the decisions that they've made notably.
Tyler: I think the, what was it, the atypical state transfer or whatever, basically like taking
Tyler: the hacked funds back out of the DAO early on, I feel like is the original sin of Ethereum.
Tyler: And then yeah, going to proof of stake and like aggressively shit talking proof of work.
Tyler: Or it could be like, you can do your own thing, man, but like you don't have to try to convince
Tyler: the world that like proof of work is like terrible and inherently broken and gonna die.
Tyler: You know, like once you start making it like an us versus them thing, then I have problems
Tyler: with that.
Tyler: And like, I'm completely happy for people to experiment with other systems and their ecosystems
Tyler: if they, you know, if the ecosystem agrees to go that way.
Chris: So I agree with both counts.
Chris: I don't even think I, I'm not even sure if I believe in proof of stake.
Chris: So I won't like say that too publicly.
Chris: I just did.
Tyler: No, I mean, I don't long term.
Tyler: I don't think proof of stake is going to be anything other than like a consolidation machine.
Tyler: And like, I think you're seeing that play out.
Jackson: So back on the, the red team thing, is there a similar thing happening in the Ethereum
Jackson: space Chris that you know of?
Chris: Well, um, there is something called AllianceDAO.
Chris: I was lucky enough to volunteer for it a couple of years ago, maybe two or three years ago
Chris: when it kicked off, uh, it's called Sealorg.
Chris: So these are the, this is like a white hat organization that just like does like free
Chris: sort of like pressure tests and audits of big public Ethereum or, and, and related like
Chris: contracts and protocols.
Chris: Um, I haven't seen much from them lately.
Chris: Um, I think like, you know, there are a couple of like high profile people involved there,
Chris: like, um, Sam CZ Sun, which is probably not a name that people know.
Chris: Um, but like, I would hope that they've transitioned to like very paradigm white hat.
Chris: Exactly.
Jackson: Yeah.
Chris: Uh, original author of the, uh, blog post, Ethereum is a dark forest, which is true.
Chris: Uh, yeah, that's a, that's a Canon event for sure.
Chris: Um, but yeah, I would hope that they have transitioned to something similar to the Bitcoin
Chris: red team stuff, which is like Kate Kimmy K three agent swarms or something like that.
Chris: Um, but honestly, I haven't been involved in a few years, so, uh, yeah, might be worth
Chris: dipping in.
Chris: Um, I think Ethereum is now, unfortunately like there are like a, a lot of corporate
Chris: interests involved and corporate interests have like a lot of resources and they, they
Chris: pressure test their own stuff as well.
Chris: So I think it's less of a, the, the public goods piece is maybe somewhat less necessary
Chris: and, and relevant as to like BTC, which I think is more really like truly the commons,
Chris: like a lot of these protocols.
Tyler: I also think that like Ethereum has had enormous incentives for people to find vulnerabilities
Tyler: for longer than Bitcoin in a way, like the, if you can find a bug in like some crucial
Tyler: smart contract and attack it, like you, you've seen how many millions have been there incentivizing
Tyler: you forever.
Tyler: Whereas something like this cold card hack is like way more subtle, like probably, uh,
Tyler: yeah, it's just like not as obvious of a target and it takes somebody just like scanning long
Tyler: tail shit with an AI to like find it.
Tyler: And I feel like a lot of the Ethereum stuff is like not necessarily long tail.
Tyler: Like a lot of the value is in probably like, you know, the top 20 smart contracts and those
Tyler: are probably scrutinized by white hats and black hats, like extremely to an extreme degree
Tyler: already before AI.
Tyler: Um, and yeah.
Chris: A hundred, like Ethereum is just in a constant state of warfare.
Chris: So like I have a contract deploy scanner that scans every contract that's deployed on Ethereum
Chris: and like there's like a new honeypot, like every minute.
Chris: Um, and it's like, it's like the bots are trying to find vulnerabilities or extract
Chris: Mev.
Chris: And then there are people deploying honeypots to exploit the bots, uh, and then there's
Chris: like two, two layers removed of this and like to work it out, like you have to read all
Chris: this and try to like, you know, unpack the discourse that's going on on chain.
Chris: So yeah, it's like, it's a totally toxic environment.
Jackson: It rules.
Jackson: A battlefield.
Jackson: It's a battlefield on the smart contract landscape.
Jackson: That's cool.
Chris: That's cool.
Jackson: That's weird that Bitcoin hasn't seen that same level of scrutiny from like hackers.
Jackson: I guess the North Korean hackers were doing something this whole time, but well, you go
Chris: for what's easiest.
Jackson: Yeah.
Tyler: Like I think certain parts of Bitcoin, like Bitcoin, like core has probably been extremely
Tyler: scrutinized.
Tyler: Um, but like random long tail Bitcoin wallets, probably less so because it's not as obvious.
Tyler: Oh, if I can find a vulnerability in this wallet, how much money can I get out of it?
Tyler: In the case of cold card, it was like a hundred million dollars, but that's because they found
Tyler: like the most catastrophic type of bug.
Tyler: And I think that the chances of finding that type of bug are pretty low.
Tyler: So it seems like there's an element of luck combining with opportunity there.
Tyler: Um, but yeah, I also feel like the, the threshold for like the thing that is our way positive
Tyler: to attack is going lower because you can just stick an agent on it.
Tyler: The tokens are cheaper.
Tyler: You don't have to spend any of your time or attention on it.
Tyler: And so like the window of things that are like worth trying to attack or like kicking
Tyler: the tires on is shifting to be like things that are even more in the tail.
Tyler: And maybe that's a lot of the, um, like turmoil that we're going to see totally like applying
Chris: my judging function, I would never bother with cold card.
Chris: I'd be like, that's the best quality.
Chris: It's like, why would I spend my time trying to find something there?
Chris: But yeah, with agents, that's worth a shot.
Jackson: Well, our admiration and gratitude goes out to the red team.
Jackson: Please protect our Bitcoin and don't let us get robbed blind.
Jackson: That concludes episode 10 totally forgot to mention episode 10, double digits, we're rolling
Jackson: high.
Jackson: Um, yeah, 10 we can all try to do it, but I don't know if it'll show and our perp survived.
Tyler: We, we didn't get liquidated.
Tyler: We only lost $36.
Jackson: All of the money we made in the past, like perps we lost.
Chris: Should I close it?
Chris: Should we cut this away or should we just let it ride to zero?
Jackson: Well, no, let's save it, dude.
Jackson: There's a lot of money, a lot of money on the line.
Jackson: And maybe next episode we'll talk about secure on place potentially.
Jackson: All right.
Jackson: We are out.
Jackson: Get after it, homies.